Amirreza Sokhankhosh



amirrezasokhankhosh79@gmail.com



+989128441565



linkedin.com/in/amirreza-sokhankhosh-9b91901a8



https://amirrezasokhankhosh.github.io/me/

Summary

This is Amirreza Sokhankhosh. I am currently a student in Khajeh Nasir Toosi University of Technology. In general, my research interest is Machine Learning. More specifically, I am interested in Reinforcement Learning based problems. I am also interested in data analysis and finding causality of a treatment on an outcome.

Experience



Teaching Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Jan 2022 - Present (4 months +)

Teaching assistant of Computer Networks.

Instructor: Dr. Rezaie

🤼 Teaching Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Jan 2022 - Present (4 months +)

Teaching assistant of Distributed Mathematics.

Instructor: Dr. Khasteh

🤼 Head Research Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months +)

Instructor: Dr.Shafiei



Research Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months +)

Instructor: Dr.Shafiei



Head Teaching Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Sep 2021 - Jan 2022 (5 months)

Head teaching assistant of Operating Systems course

Instructor: Dr.Shafiei



🤼 Head Teaching Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Jan 2021 - Jul 2021 (7 months)

Head teaching assistant of Algorithm Design course

Instructor: Dr.Shafiei

Teaching Assistant

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Jan 2021 - Jul 2021 (7 months)

Teaching assistant of Operating System course

Instructor: Dr.Khanmirza

Rack End Developer

Nadin Soft

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020 (6 months)

Backend development with Adonis is framework.

Education



K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering 2018 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Reinforcement Learning Specialization - University of Alberta

9JDL9754G579



💢 A Crash Course in Causality: Inferring Causal Effects from Observational Data -

Penn Medicine, University of Pennsylvania Health System 845YRUUE8YA6

Supervised Machine Learning: Regression - IBM

TGQCB4DJ84F7

Skills

python • Node.js • Reinforcement Learning • java • AdonisJs • Javascript • Django • Telegram bot